{"data":[{"question":"I'm busy _____ the moment, but I can see you tomorrow.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"I went to a nice restaurant _____ my birthday.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"Our team scored ____ the last few seconds of the game.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- In the last few seconds","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"I'm going to Europe _____ May.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"I like to go to the mountains _____ the summer.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Use in with months, seasons, years, centuries","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"The Great Depression began _____ the early 1930's.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- In the beginning of\/ in the early","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"What are you doing _____ the weekend?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- On: Use on with dates and specific days, with weekend, in American English","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"The hills are covered with wildflowers _____ the springtime.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"Use in with months, seasons, years, centuries","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"Unemployment was much lower _____ the third quarter.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for seasons, months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"},{"question":"Professor Andrews only became famous _____ his old age.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for seasons, months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"2"}]}